[
	{
		"question":"Coprastasophobia is the fear of what?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Corporate Greed",
				"Door-to-Door Vacuum Salesmen",
				"Constipation",
				"Public Speaking"
			],
		"answer":"Constipation",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"In Minnesota, it is illegal to tease what type of animal?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Skunks",
				"Bears Fans",
				"Moose",
				"Small Children"
			],
		"answer":"Skunks",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"In Kansas, it is illegal to put what on cherry pie?",
		"choices":
			[
				"more cherry pie, forming a cherry pie sandwich",
				"Ice Cream",
				"Whipped Cream",
				"Small Children"
			],
		"answer":"Ice Cream",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"In North Carolina, it's illegal to hold a meeting or demonstration while...",
		"choices":
			[
				"",
				"Wearing a Mask",
				"",
				""
			],
		"answer":"Wearing a Mask",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"In Gainesville GA, it is illegal to eat fried chicken with...",
		"choices":
			[
				"Ketchup",
				"Mayonnaise",
				"a Fork",
				"Unsweet Iced Tea"
			],
		"answer":"a Fork",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"In Blythe CA, it is illegal to wear cowboy boots unless you own how many cows?",
		"choices":
			[
				"over 9000",
				"2",
				"0.. what?",
				"1"
			],
		"answer":"2",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"In 1986, Clint Eastwood became mayor of Carmel-by-the-Sea in order to what?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Research for an upcoming role",
				"Think `The Purge`, but real life",
				"Repeal a ban on public ice cream",
				"Yell at an empty chair"
			],
		"answer":"Repeal a ban on public ice cream",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"The electric chair was invented by...",
		"choices":
			[
				"Thomas Edison",
				"a Scientist",
				"the Military-Industrial Complex",
				"a Dentist"
			],
		"answer":"a Dentist",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"Butterflies taste...",
		"choices":
			[
				"with their feet",
				"with their tongues",
				"with their wings",
				"like snozberries"
			],
		"answer":"with their feet",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"Crickets hear...",
		"choices":
			[
				"with their feet",
				"with their tongues",
				"with their wings",
				"with their knees"
			],
		"answer":"with their knees",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"What animal can't jump?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Elephant",
				"White Men",
				"Penguin",
				"Panda"
			],
		"answer":"Elephant",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"What was the first novel written on a typewriter?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Moby Dick",
				"The Adventures of Tom Sawyer",
				"A Tale of Two Cities",
				"50 Shades of Grey"
			],
		"answer":"The Adventures of Tom Sawyer",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"Nicolas Cage won an Academy Award for `Best Actor` for which movie?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Con Air",
				"Leaving Las Vegas",
				"National Treasure 3 (come back to this in 5 years)",
				"The Wicker Man"
			],
		"answer":"Leaving Las Vegas",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"Which city is Kansas City located in?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Missouri",
				"Kansas",
				"The United States of America",
				"it's not"
			],
		"answer":"it's not",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"`Tina` in `Tina Fey` is short for what?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Christina",
				"Stamatina",
				"Bettina",
				"Martina"
			],
		"answer":"Stamatina",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"What is the national animal of Colombia?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Andean Condor",
				"Jaguar",
				"",
				""
			],
		"answer":"Andean Condor",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"The 1956 Summer Olympics were held in Australia with the exception of the equestrian events. In which European country did the equestrian events take place?",
		"choices":
			[
				"France",
				"England",
				"The United States of America",
				"Sweden"
			],
		"answer":"Sweden",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"The Shiba Inu is a Japanese hunting doge.  Inu is Japanese for `dog`, what does Shiba mean?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Brushwood",
				"Forest",
				"Snoop",
				"Woodland"
			],
		"answer":"Brushwood",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"In `Beauty and the Beast`, what is the name of Belle's horse?",
		"choices":
			[
				"LeFou",
				"Philippe",
				"Maurice",
				"Beast"
			],
		"answer":"Philippe",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"In `Aladdin`, what is the name of Aladdin's monkey friend?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Apu",
				"Iago",
				"Abu",
				"Aladdin Jr."
			],
		"answer":"Abu",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"What was the first Disney animated movie to be adapted as a Broadway show?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Snow White",
				"Beauty and the Beast",
				"Lion King",
				"Frozen"
			],
		"answer":"Snow White",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"What is the name of the cat in Cinderella?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Dog",
				"Satan Claws",
				"El Diablo",
				"Lucifer"
			],
		"answer":"Lucifer",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"In `Brave`, Merida uses what weapon to compete for her own hand in marriage?",
		"choices":
			[
				"the Patriarchy",
				"Friendship",
				"Universal Suffrage",
				"Bow and Arrow"
			],
		"answer":"Bow and Arrow",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"Ouagadougou is the capital of which African country?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Chad",
				"Burkina Faso",
				"Eritrea",
				"Djibouti"
			],
		"answer":"Burkina Faso",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"In `Charlie and the Chocolate Factory`, which character disqualification scared the absolute hell out of child-me?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Augustus Gloop",
				"Violet Beauregarde",
				"Mike Teavee",
				"Veruca Salt"
			],
		"answer":"Augustus Gloop",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"Which animal sleeps for only five minutes a day?",
		"choices":
			[
				"a koala",
				"a giraffe",
				"me on a workday",
				"a beaver"
			],
		"answer":"a giraffe",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"The bikini was originally called the what?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Poke",
				"Range",
				"Half",
				"Atom"
			],
		"answer":"Atom",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"Which of these planets rotates clockwise?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Uranus",
				"Mercury",
				"Pluto",
				"Venus"
			],
		"answer":"Venus",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"In China, why must you never stand chopsticks upgright in your rice?",
		"choices":
			[
				"They resemble candles being burnt for lovers who've left",
				"They resemble joss sticks used in rituals for the deceased",
				"They resemble the male and female at war in families",
				"They resemble knives pointed up towards heaven"
			],
		"answer":"They resemble joss sticks used in rituals for the deceased",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"What does a pagophagiac eat?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Fingernails",
				"Ash",
				"Pips",
				"Ice"
			],
		"answer":"Ice",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"A fysigunkus is a person who lacks what?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Humor",
				"Wisdom",
				"Curiosity",
				"Discipline"
			],
		"answer":"Curiosity",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"What color is a newborn Dalmatian?",
		"choices":
			[
				"white",
				"black",
				"black with white spots",
				"white with black spots"
			],
		"answer":"white",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"Which country has the lowest average ground level in the world?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Republic of Mauritius",
				"Holland",
				"The Seychelles",
				"Republic of the Maldives"
			],
		"answer":"Republic of the Maldives",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"What is the loudest animal on Earth?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Blue Whale",
				"Elephant",
				"Sperm Whale",
				"Rush Limbaugh"
			],
		"answer":"Blue Whale",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"Which country has a beaver as its national emblem?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Kazakhstan",
				"Poland",
				"Canada",
				"Beavertonfieldville"
			],
		"answer":"Canada",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"True or False - white rhinos are white.",
		"choices":
			[
				"True",
				"False",
				"Maybe",
				"How can white rhinos be real if our eyes aren't real?"
			],
		"answer":"False",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"What is the world's most venemous fish?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Scorpion fish",
				"Lion Fish",
				"Stonefish",
				"Poison McPoisonface"
			],
		"answer":"Stonefish",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"What is the fastest swimming animal?",
		"choices":
			[
				"Orca",
				"Michael Phelps",
				"Swordfish",
				"Sailfish"
			],
		"answer":"Sailfish",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"",
		"choices":
			[
				"",
				"",
				"",
				""
			],
		"answer":"",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"",
		"choices":
			[
				"",
				"",
				"",
				""
			],
		"answer":"",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"",
		"choices":
			[
				"",
				"",
				"",
				""
			],
		"answer":"",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"",
		"choices":
			[
				"",
				"",
				"",
				""
			],
		"answer":"",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"",
		"choices":
			[
				"",
				"",
				"",
				""
			],
		"answer":"",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"",
		"choices":
			[
				"",
				"",
				"",
				""
			],
		"answer":"",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"",
		"choices":
			[
				"",
				"",
				"",
				""
			],
		"answer":"",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"",
		"choices":
			[
				"",
				"",
				"",
				""
			],
		"answer":"",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"",
		"choices":
			[
				"",
				"",
				"",
				""
			],
		"answer":"",
		"type":"mc"
	}, {
		"question":"",
		"choices":
			[
				"",
				"",
				"",
				""
			],
		"answer":"",
		"type":"mc"
	}
]